Privacy Policy
==============

Rethink DNS + Firewall are anti-surveillance tools first and foremost: It is absolutely against our ethos, then, to track users of our apps and services, or sell any information whatsoever to any third-party in any form, pseudo-anonymized, de-anonymized, anonymized, aggregated, or otherwise.

App Privacy Policy
------------------

We do not collect, sell, license, share any data (personally identifiable or otherwise) from the [Rethink DNS + Firewall Android app](https://rethinkdns.com/download).

Revision: 21 Oct 2020

* The app is free of any trackers, spyware, ads, or loggers whatsoever. This can be, to an extent, ascertained from our code which is open-source on [GitHub](https://github.com/celzero/brave-android-app).
* The app does not use or depend on or embed any third-party services in its default setting. The only exception is Google PlayStore (see their [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US)) which is used as an app distribution channel.
* The app does not collect any debug or diagnostic data unless you explicitly choose to share it with us, for example, over [\[email protected\]](https://rethinkdns.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

DNS Privacy Policy
------------------

We do not collect, sell, license, share any personally identifiable data from our DNS resolvers. The [code is open source](https://github.com/serverless-dns/serverless-dns/) so you may inspect it yourself or deploy to your servers.

Revision: 14 Oct 2022

For stub resolvers: `https://basic.rethinkdns.com/<config>` and `https://sky.rethinkdns.com/<config-id>`

* The resolver does not collect personally identifiable information nor does it seek to profile a user or a group of users.
* This DNS-over-HTTPS resolver runs on Cloudflare's network whose privacy policy you may find [here](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).

For recursive resolver: `https://max.rethinkdns.com/<config>`

* The resolver does not collect personally identifiable information nor does it seek to profile a user or a group of users.
* This DNS-over-HTTPS and DNS-over-TLS recursive resolver runs on Fly.io whose privacy policy you may find [here](https://fly.io/legal/privacy-policy/).

+----------------------+---------------+---------------+-----------+---------------+
| Data                 | Sold / Shared | Collected     | Retained  | Usage         |
+----------------------+---------------+---------------+-----------+---------------+
| Domain Name          | No            | No            | --        | --            |
| Client IP            | No            | No            | --        | --            |
| User Agent           | No            | No            | --        | --            |
| Device ID            | No            | No            | --        | --            |
| Anything else        | No            | No            | --        | --            |
+----------------------+---------------+---------------+-----------+---------------+
| Rethink DNS resolvers do not log requests.                                       |
+----------------------------------------------------------------------------------+

Website Privacy Policy
----------------------

We do not collect, sell, license, share any data (including cookies) from our any of our web pages at [rethinkdns.com](https://rethinkdns.com/).

Revision: 20 Mar 2021

* The website does not set any cookies or attempt to track a user in way or form.
* The website does not embed any third-party analytics or services that may track users.
* The website does not log any interactions a visiting user has with the website.
* The website and app download link are hosted and served by Cloudflare, respectively, whose privacy policy you may find [here](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).

Explanation
-----------

If you spot any ambiguity with privacy policies outlined on this page then please [\[email protected\]](https://rethinkdns.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we would update it right away..

Revision: 21 Oct 2020

* Personally identifiable information: Any data that can be traced back to the user including (but not limited to) a combination of IP addresses, name, device-id, advertisement-id, and location.
* Non personally identifiable information: Aggregrated (summarized) data and anonymized data scrubbed off any personally identifiable information.
* Collect: Data stored by Rethink.
* Sell: Data sold to third parties.
* License: Restricted access to data collected by Rethink to third parties.
* Share: Permanent access to data collected by Rethink to third parties.

Get notified as we announce more tools

 Subscribe

No spam. Only love.

Part of Mozilla Builders MVP program [](https://builders.mozilla.community/)

[\[email protected\]](https://rethinkdns.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* PRODUCT

* ABOUT

* COMMUNITY

Google Play and the Google Play logo are trademarks of Google LLC.

BraveDNS is now RethinkDNS.
